bandai.com 2009-03-24

# Bandai.com - Privacy Policy: find toys for Power Rangers, Ben 10, Dragon Ball, Tamagotchi, and Action Figures

We here at Bandai America Incorporated (BAI) make the safety and privacy of children a top concern. This notice is being supplied in compliance with the [Children's Online Privacy Protection Act](http://www.coppa.org/) (COPPA). Bandai attempts to adhere/or intends to comply with CARU's Self-Regulatory Guidelines for Children's Advertising.

**What information will Bandai collect?**  
While visiting the BAI website we may request and store personally identifiable information for the purpose stated on the page where the information is requested. Such information may include name, nickname, birth date, contact information (including address, phone number, and email address), gender, product interests, hobbies, and parental contact information. If you are under the age of 13, parental consent to provide this information will be required. We will contact the parent or guardian indicated to advise why the personal information is being requested, to advise what will be done with the personally identifiable information and to seek permission to collect this information. At no time is any personal information ever collected automatically, it is only collected when voluntarily provided.

If an unsolicited request is submitted by a user under 13 years of age, their first name and email address is only kept for purposes of sending a response. None of the information will be used outside the scope of the original request made by the child. Once the reply is generated, the email address is deleted from our system.

Additional information such as the web pages visited, links followed, and amount of time spent viewing content on the BAI website may be collected automatically and stored in a personally identifiable fashion, provided the child is a registered user of the BAI website.

Other information may be automatically recorded by our web server to provide usage statistics and information so that we can provide a better experience at the BAI website. This information is not personally identifiable.

And, of course, we here at Bandai want to make sure everyone has fun, so we will not require children to surrender any information as a requirement to participate in any section of the website unless that information is essential to the function of that section.

**Do you use cookies?**  
The BAI website may make use of cookies (small pieces of information placed on your computer by our website) for information collection purposes. Any information provided by these cookies will not be personally identifiable and is solely used to improve your experience at our site. We dot not passively connect personally identifiable information through the use of cookies.

**What do you do with the information collected?**  
The information we collect may, at times, be used for the following:

  * Notification of contest winners and qualifiers
  * Promotional, marketing, and informative mailings related to Bandai products
  * Order or request fulfillment
  * Internal Bandai marketing and demographic research
  * BAI website tracking

All information collected will be used solely by Bandai and not given, sold, or otherwise transferred to third parties in a personally identifiable form.

**How can I contact you?**  
At any time, a parent may request to view the personal information collected by BAI related to that parent's child, may request their child's information to be deleted from our system or to request that further information not be collected from their child. To initiate such a request, email [webmaster@bandai.com](http://www.bandai.com/contact/contact.html) stating the full name the child used to register at the BAI website.

If you have any questions or comments on this policy, please feel free to email [webmaster@bandai.com](http://www.bandai.com/contact/contact.html) or contact to us at:

> Bandai America Incorporated  
>  5551 Katella Avenue  
>  Cypress, CA 90630  
>  714.816.9560  
> 

In order to be in compliance with the legal requirements or to provide better customer service, BAI reserves the right to modify this policy. Any changes to the policy will be posted on our site. Thank you for taking the time to read this policy.

_Effective date: 06/24/2004_
